# Kelvin Kelly

## **Junior Engineer**

Turnersville, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Kelvin-Kelly/1ca8a36828e5823c

Experienced, reliable engineer and IT professional with 9+ years experience in production support and systems operations. Ability to oversee complex troubleshooting operations while providing exceptional customer service and quality assurance. Looking to acquire a challenging position as Cisco Network Engineer, where my knowledge and experience will provide added value within I.T.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Junior Engineer

Com TechSoloutions L.L.C - Township of Randolph, NJ - 2013 to 2013

- Oversee and report all incident reports, service level agreements and network escalations to network manager.
- Develop, document, implement and maintain systems management strategies, policies and procedures including security, support, training and installation procedures.
- Configure network switches with HSRP for high availability and inter-VLAN routing.
- Configure and deploy 2960-X, 3750-X and 3850-X as access and distribution switches.
- Configure VLAN, STP and Port Security on switches to create a secure, reliable and high available LAN.
- Upgrade cisco routers with latest or recommended IOS software.
- Configure and troubleshoot Layer 3 routing protocols (EIGRP, OSPF).
- Work with Internet providers to turn up WAN MPLS connectivity to new remote sites.
- Use Netflow and Wireshark for network analysis.

#### **NOC Engineer**

Comcast - Mount Laurel, NJ - 2013 to 2013

Analyze data and metrics, interpret operational trends, and react to changes in expected system behaviors and patterns in a timely manner.

- Handle telephone and e-mail escalations from customer care, local markets, engineering, or management.
- Maintain accurate recordkeeping, incident timelines, turnover logs and status reports.
- Perform routine maintenance on systems including change requests, data gathering requests and patch implementations.
- Correlate events across multiple subsystems to narrow down potential root causes of problems.
- Coordinate troubleshooting calls, identifying service-impacting events and recruiting additional resources as necessary.
- Reconcile minor problems with UNIX and Microsoft Windows systems.
- Collaborate with engineering teams to identify and resolve technical issues.

# **Production Support Engineer**

Medco - Willingboro, NJ - 2006 to 2013

Maintained overall operation of the Automated Pharmacy Command Center (APCC.)

- Accurately and promptly resolved performance issues related to supported systems.
- Utilized VERITAS NetBackup to perform system backups. Scheduled and distributed backup reports to department manager.

- Created custom Structured Query Language (SQL) queries per customer requests and delivered results in a timely manner.
- Developed and implemented Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) for Automated Pharmacy Command Center.
- Performed Operational Qualification (OQ), Performance Qualification (PQ) and Integrated Testing (IT.)
- Ensured quality assurance goals were achieved by submitting and reviewing customer satisfaction surveys. Took corrective action when necessary.
- Conducted daily audits and quality audits. Reviewed and reported aging reports; presented to senior management.
- Supported off-site production through remote access and frequent communication via VNC (Virtual Network Computing) application.
- Trained and oriented new employees in overall departmental responsibilities and pharmacy operations overview.
- Recommended new software applications and communications products to enhance department speed and efficiency.

## **Production Supervisor**

Express Scripts - Willingboro, NJ - 2002 to 2006

Assured company's production, quality, and service were met on a daily basis

- Managed all departmental staffing needs
- Provide overview training for Quality Response Team and Electro Mechanical Techs
- Assists in establishing and implementing work stream goals, objectives, and operating procedures.
- Work collaboratively with leadership across the network to proactively manage service.
- Provide guidance and analysis to managers and directors on key indicator trends and recommend actions to optimize performance and reduce barriers that impact patient service
- Assisted in developing service plans within the department to ensure swift resolution of patient and client issues.
- Responsible for maintaining quality, service, compliance, safety and cost objectives for ADDS, ALPS, and AP departments.
- Responsible for hiring, training, coaching and developing leads and support staff
- Understand the functionality of the router, PAC, and WMS to facilitate necessary research
- Motivate staff, affect meaningful change and ensure accountability of direct reports as well as others involved
  in the process
- Monitor, research, and resolve high level prescriptions from order receipt to manifesting
- Ensure completion of escalated and aged order throughout pharmacy
- Provided analysis and identification of key indicator trends.
- Oversaw a Lead serving as point of escalation for issues requiring a higher degree of expertise or direction to solve

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelors of Science**

DeVry University - Philadelphia, PA

MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US

Branch: Army National Guard

Rank: E4

September 1994 to November 2001